### **Andrew Childre**

720-560-9688 andrewchildre@gmail.com Erie, Colorado

Portfolio Site
Email
Linkedin
Github

#### **Profile**

I have completed the General Assembly software engineering immersive program. Currently I am freelancing on real world projects with a Sr. Developer. I have experience in completing complex projects with little oversight. I have worked with high performing teams, and am highly motivated. I produce quality work, and would be a valuable addition to anyone's team.

## **Technologies**

HTML | CSS | Javascript | Typescript | jQuery | Material-UI | Bootstrap | Git | Github | React | React Native | Node | MongoDB | Express | SQL | PostgreSQL | Python | DjangoDB | VS Code

# **Education | Training**

GA General Assembly: Software Engineering Immersive

United States Marine Corps: Aviation maintenance, Honor Graduate, NCO Leadership Graduate

**Corporate Schools** 

Supervisor Leadership School Automotive Fleet Training School, Aircraft Ground Equipment training

### **Experience**

### Hazmat Tanker Transport 2021 - 2015

Safely transport different petroleum products to and from different plants and refineries.

Follow all DOT, OSHA, and client requirements.

Identify safety risks ahead of time, and make corrections.

### Fleet Supervisor, FedEx Freight, Henderson, CO 2012 - 2015

Managed Fleet of 500+ vehicles across several states, a national trailer fleet, and coordinated maintenance scheduling.

Supervised 23 maintenance personnel and support staff.

Optimized mechanic and maintenance schedules for greater productivity, always met dispatch schedules, and reduced maintenance costs.

Created best practices for metrics that were missed.

### Fleet Manager/Supervisor, Con-way Freight, Henderson, CO 2010 – 2012

Managed a multi-million dollar budget, with a fleet of 250 vehicles, and a national trailer fleet

Supervised 14 technicians and support staff.

Implemented procedures to correct parts inventory accountability.

Negotiated contracts with outside vendors.

# Fleet Manager/ Supervisor, UPS, Sparks, NV 2003 – 2010

Oversee multi-million maintenance budget, a fleet of 200 vehicles.

Completed safety training on time and under budget.

Ensure vendor accountability with quarterly audits.

Sustain a preventative maintenance program, including monitoring, reviewing, and analyzing existing procedures.

Support UPS objectives to maximize fleet safety and performance.